How do you feel about Ramzan
Как относишься к Рамзану
Kadyrov to Ramzan Kadyrov Yes, I don’t feel at all
Кадырову к Рамзану Кадырову Да никак не
Well, how is he a hero of Russia,
отношусь Ну как он герой России же
like, who hasn’t been a hero of Russia,
вроде да кто только не был героем России
wait, well, Hero of Russia, like Hello,
подожди ну Герой России типа Здравствуй
Good evening, Hello
Добрый вечер Привет
guys, How are you doing? I’m from the city of
пацаны Как дела у вас Я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from? We’re from
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Мы из
St.  St. Petersburg And how do you communicate so that
санкт-петербурга А чем общаетесь
everything, that is, well, about politics? To be honest, I’m already tired of talking about everything about sports, about the Soviet Union,
всём о спорте о Советском Союзе скажешь
and what about the Soviet Union exactly? Well,
а что о Советском Союзе именно Ну в том
including about sports in the Soviet Union and about
числе и о спорте в Советском Союзе и о
certain pros and cons that
определённых плюсах и минусах которые
were in the Soviet Union And you're some kind of
были в Советском Союзе А ты какой-то
athlete Well, I'm into sports and I'm a
спортсмен Ну я увлекаюсь спортом а
football
футбольный
fan It's
фанат
cool and a football fan Which
Прикольно а футбольный фанат За какой
club do you race for?
клуб гоняешь
Well, no one in Russia races for
Ну у нас уже никто не гоняет в России за
clubs anymore, it's like they've already made fans,
клубы у нас это как бы уже фана сделали
yes Well, here it’s just  to
да Ну у у нас просто это
eradicate this, in fact, I think that from
искоренить на самом деле я считаю что с
some point of view this is Correct Because
какой-то стороны это Правильно Потому
even now
что даже сейчас на футбольные матчи
when I go to football matches, a lot of families come with
когда хожу очень много семей приходит с
small children, this is cool. I like
детьми маленькими это круто Мне нравится
that sport has acquired such a look
что спорт приоб Ну приобретает такой вид
from one Rhone to the other. Of course I miss it
с одной Роны с другой Конечно я скучаю
At that time, the bikes were shorter, in general, they
по тем временам велы короче в общем
completely made the Russian
э менты полностью сделали российский
Okolofutbol like the cops. Well, I wouldn’t
Околофутбол под ментовский Да ну я бы не
say like the cops, they just made it
сказал под ментовский просто сделали его
Radika, the cops, not like the cops, but
Радика ментовский не под ментовский а
completely the cops. Well, radicalism
ментовский полностью Ну радикализм
just went away. Right-wing views also
просто ушёл правый взгляды тоже уже
remained in the 2000s in the early
остались в нулевых в начале десятых
1900s.  I remember the stories when our people
Раньше я помню истории Когда наши в
got into a mess with the locals in the center of Moscow,
замес с местными ступали в центре Москвы
right in the center in the huh 100 to 100 people,
прямо в центре в хах 100 на 100 человек
it was of course horror. Well, it’s impossible for
это был конечно ужас Ну это нельзя чтобы
this to happen, there were
такое происходило
fights in the center of the city between people,
замесы в центре города были между людьми
there were children there, there were women who could
там же дети там женщины кто может
get under all this  kneading, well, why the hell is
попасть под это всё под замес ну нафиг
it necessary? Yes, how do you feel about how you feel
это надо Да как относишь как относишься
about How do you feel about Ramzan
к Как относишься к Рамзану
Kadyrov about Ramzan Kadyrov? Well, I don’t
Кадырову к Рамзану Кадырову Да никак не
think so at all. Well, he’s a hero of Russia,
отношусь Ну как он герой России же
like, who hasn’t been a hero of Russia?
вроде да кто только не был героем России
Well, like a Hero of Russia, like, well, I don’t
по Ну как Герой России типа ну мне всё
care. I’m speaking in  Ramzan Kadyrov What’s
равно Я говорю на Рамзана Кадырова А что
wrong?
не так
I’m not a Chechen. I’ve never been to
я не являюсь чеченцем Я никогда не был В
Chechnya. Maybe someday I’ll come as a tourist.
Чечне может когда-то приеду как Турист
You’re a Russian and they’re
посмо Ты же россиянин и они
Russians. Yes, I’m a Russian and they’re Russians.
россияне Да я россиянин и они россияне
But how can I treat the CMU? How do I
ну а как я могу КМУ относиться как я
feel about them? I’m not  I know the head of the
отношусь к там я не знаю главе
Jewish Autonomous Okrug Yes, [ __ ], I
еврейского автономного округа Да [__]
don’t know how I feel, I don’t follow, I’m not
не знаю как я отношусь не слежу не
interested, and you read this book, you
интересно а ты эту книжку ты книжку
read Grant’s book, no, that’s what the battle at sea was like
читал нет вот это что сражение на море у
in your childhood. Well, I can’t
тебя в детстве ещё Ну так я не могу
say that I’ve been delving into it since
сказать что я вникал оно у тебя с
childhood  worth it Yes yes yes it’s cool it
детства стоит Да да да прикольно мне
seems to me that it was released not so long ago
кажется что она не так давно выпущена
now I’ll even
сейчас даже
watch one moment of the Secondary School Well, the year 2019
посмотрю один момент СШ Ну год 2019
may not be exactly not in this I think
может не точно не в этом Мне кажется
later we’ll ask before we’ll
позже нам раньше нам
go while I’m looking at What’s up with you
пось пока я по посмот Что как дела у вас
about the World Cup here you communicate with
о ЧМ здесь общаетесь
different people  like I’m looking for and
разных людей типа ищу и вот
here I talk about
там общаюсь о
different things Well, about politics and more Yes,
разных Ну о политике да побольше Да вот
you’re interesting Yes, some guys are
вы интересны Да какие-то пацаны
now at the end, look at the
сейчас в конце посмотри там тираж
publishing house’s circulation there Well, we’ve already talked to politics somehow
издательство Ну мы так политике уже
meanly,
пообщались както подло
but how do you feel about Denis
а как вы относитесь к Денису
Kapustin who to Denis Kapustin
капустину кому к Денису капустину Это
Who is this  Russian Dobrovo Russian
кто русский доброво русский
Volunteer Corps Well, in
добровольческий корпус А ну к ним на
fact, it’s negative towards them, rather much more
деле негативно скорее намного причём
negatively good, and towards
негативно хорош а к
Milkov’s ses, I can say about the Schniks
милькову сес я можно скажу поводу шников
For the most part, I come from a
По большей части выходца как раз таки из
fan base, too, and that’s why I
фанатки тоже да я же поэтому тебя и
asked you, yes, I’m just from certain companies  I did
спросил да из определённых фирм я просто
n’t know him to be honest What’s his name
не знал его честно говоря Как зовут в
and there’s also Sparta and
том числе и там есть и Спарта и динамики
some dynamics and our guys from St. Petersburg Well, how do I
немного и наши ребята из Питера Ну как
feel about the guys, they have the right views, they
отношусь ребята правы взглядов
support their own ideas Well, they went
поддерживают свои какие-то идеи Ну пошли
against their country there Well, there are no
против там своей страны Ну
traitors, there are no currents of opinion Maybe it’s not
предатели токи зрения нет Может это не
them  went against your country Maybe it was
они пошли против своей страны Может это
you who went against your
вы пошли против своей
country How do you feel about
страны Как относишься к
I didn’t go anywhere I’ll tell you how you
Я никуда не ходил расскажу вам как
feel about Martsinkevich
относитесь к марцинкевичу
uh I understood it sharply negatively I think that his
э резко негативно понял Я считаю что его
ideology and his actions which were
идеология и его поступки которые были
Horrible how you feel about Melchakov from the
Ужас как относитесь к Мельчакова из
Rusich Well, that’s what I understand too  right-wing
русича Ну тоже я так понимаю правые
guys who run from Kolovrat, well,
ребята которые бегают с коловрата ну
ordinary rights, nothing like that. So, what do
обычные права ничего такого Так а как
you think of
вам
his right-wing ideology?
идеология его правая
Melchakova is just an ideology. That’s
Мельчакова раз бывает идеология Вот
exactly Melchakova’s ideology from Rusich.
именно Мельчакова из русича
If I’m not mistaken, they are there for the
идеология Если не ошибаюсь Они же там по
most part, if they use Kolovrat and
большей части если используют Коловрат и
all this topic, they are pagans for the most
всю эту тематику они язычники по большей
part. How  I know, I’m not asking about religion.
части Как зна Я же не про религию
Well, you know the Milchaks
спрашиваю Ну вот мильчаков вы знаете
have the right to paganism with pagan
есть право язычества с языческими
biases. The fact is that this Rusich,
уклонами Дело в том что вот этот Русич
look, Russian Nazis who are fighting
смотри российские нацисты которые воюют
in Ukraine against Ukraine are killing like that. It’s
в Украине против Украины так
more like right-wing guys, well,
убива Это скорее правые ребята ну
they’re killing Yazovites, I can’t
убивают с язовцев не могу нацистами
call them Nazis, that is  you will support that
назвать то есть вы поддержите что вот
this Rusich Melkov came to Ukraine to
этот Русич Мельков приехал в Украину
kill the Slavs, do you support or not
убивать славян поддерживаете или не
support Azov Azov Azov did not come to a
поддержите Азов Азов Азов не приезжал в
foreign country Azov is defending their country Azov is
чужую Азов защищают свою страну Азов
heroes and the lion came to a foreign country
герои а льв приехал в чужую страну
to kill people
убивать людей
he has an ideology you need to ask him
у него идеология надо у него спрашивать
you are the Musorsky office
вы мусорские конторские
truth Why is this so  and you
правда Почему так и душка у вас уже
don’t have a darling anymore or
нет либо
we don’t have a sweetheart why give an argument
нешка у нас нет почему аргументируйте
Look, I’ll say
Смотри я скажу потому
because your
что твою
country is being destroyed by a gang of small bastards
страну уничтожает шайка небольших прохин
you Russian Slavs there the Armed Forces are disappearing there are fewer and
вас русских славян там стаёт ВС меньше и
fewer Slavic cities
меньше славянских городов уже не
left
осталось
almost no Slavic city,
почти сяй какой Славянский город
look again, not the first time I  I
смотрите опять же не первый раз я это
’m saying this for this day, how the
говорю за этот день как уничтожает
Russian people are destroying if 8 7% of the ethnic
русский народ если 8 7% этнически
population of the Russian
населения Российской
Federation is approximately, well, such
федераци примерно ну такая
statistics are the question of how many Tajiks
статистика вопрос скольким таджикам
were given citizenship last year
выдали в прошлом году
Yes, how many Tajiks How many
гражданство Да скольким таджико Сколько
Tajiks received citizenship last year
таджиков получили в прошлом году
I don’t know how much
гражданство я не знаю сколько
citizenship I can roughly understand From
гражданства Я примерно могу понять По
work  how much
работе сколько
at I now
при Я сейчас
look like this, in January-March
так так вот смотрите э в январе-марте
2023 it turns out 3 months of the twenty-
2023 это получается 3 месяца двадцать
third year. Here is the first news:
третьего года Вот первая новость
more than
гражданство России получили более
106,000 foreign citizens received Russian citizenship, most
106.000 иностранных граждан большую
of whom are residents of
часть из которых составляют жители
Tajikistan. That is, in 3 months of the
Таджикистана То есть за 3 месяца
twenty-third year, a hundred thousand
двадцать третьего года сотня тысяч
Tajiks received  yes yes Well, listen, given
таджиков получили да да Ну слушайте при
the population of the Russian Federation, these are
населении Российской Федерации это
quite acceptable figures.
достаточно приемлемые цифры
Why are they unacceptable? How much does this
Почему неприемлемы скоко меня это
suit me? Personally, I can’t say that
устраивает Лично я не могу сказать что
this bothers me in any way. Come on,
меня это как-то беспокоит Дава давай так
look at it like this. In Russia, only in the last
смотри В России только за последние там
3 years,
3 года
about
да порядка
1% of citizens have become
1% граждан стало
Tajiks.  we are not talking about those who
таджиками е мы не говорим те ко
come and who go further How many
приезжают и которые дальше лези Сколько
children do
детей у
you have so far, not at all How many
вас пока нисколько не сколько А сколько
children does a Tajik have at the age of 20? Well, I think that
детей у таджика в 20 лет Ну думаю что
quite a lot, yes. The question is how many
достаточно много много да Вопрос сколько
Slavs will be in Moscow in 20-30
славян будет в Москве через 20-30
years? How many Englishmen are there?
лет Столько сколько англичан в нне прин
those
те
Mosk you are sitting you are already Dead boys
Моск вы сидите вы уже Мёртвые пацаны вам
how old are you
по сколько лет
Well a little less let's say thirty I'm
Ну чуть меньше скажем так тридцати мне
thirty That is you in short Even you
ну тридцати То есть вы короче Даже у вас
don't Even uh let's say how it is Pushing
нету Даже ээ скажем как это Потяг
in Russian the desire to reproduce Yes the
по-русски стремление к размножению Да
desire to create a family Why
стремление к созданию семьи Почему
Why there is a desire  Why
Почему стремление есть Почему стремление
is there an aspiration? Why is there not an aspiration? A stepladder doesn’t
есть Почему не стремление стремянка не
work, or how, well, how an aspiration,
работает или как ну как стремление
look,
смотри
uh, you are for Slavic
ээ вы за славянскую
Russia
Русь
Russia Russia is a multinational
Россию Россия многонациональное
state,
государство у
we have the Russian people - this is a state
нас русский народ - это государственный
people who form the state inside. It’s
народ который образует государст нутри
clear. In principle, go there, here you are, I
Понятно В принципе поди ты вот ты я тебя
see you by the epicanthus, you’re not
вижу по эпикантуса ты не
Russian, he’s Russian, he’s Russian, you’re not
русский вот он рус он русский ты не
Russian, you have a g he rui I’m not Russian, but
русский у тебя г он руй Я не русский а
what am
то что
I, look at Russian hair, what does it have to do with
я вот смотрите Руссы волос ме так причём
What kind of hair does every Tajik have, such
Какие волосы у каждого таджика такие
hair Look,
волосы Смотри
you’ve seen the skin of Rumi, you have a
ты кожи видели Руми во у тебя разрез
Turkic eye shape It’s because  balaclavas because of the
глаз тюркский Это из-за балаклавы изза
balaclava because of the bakla I never
балаклавы изза бакла я никогда в
went to Balaklava, I didn’t see people in
Балаклаве не ходил не видел людей в
Balaklava, look you have epicanthus,
Балаклаве смотри у тебя эпикантус есть
yes, that is, you, that is, you determine by epicanthus
да то есть ты то есть вы по эпикантус
Nationality is not racial,
определяете Национальность не расовый
it’s
это
clear who did this
чётко которые так делали
in 1945, in my opinion there are no more of them
в соро пятом по-моему больше их не
left Well  that is, look at
осталось Ну то есть смотри
this Russian and which Yes, he
вот вот этот русский да который Да он
really doesn’t
реально не
reproduce, he doesn’t reproduce, the guys
размножается он не размножается ребята
from Tajikistan reproduce, the Chechens
из Таджикистана размножаются чеченцы
reproduce in
размножаются в
Chechnya, they saw it, it’s sung, I’m a
Чечне видели поется я
Tajik, I’ll have children. Not you, no, no,
таджик у меня дети буду Не ты Не не сри
I don’t know who you are, but you’re not Russian, I haven’t
я не знаю кто ты но ты не русский Я не
determined
определил
myself now, not now, look, I’ll read it to you right now,
себя сечас не теперь смотри я вам сейчас
how much Russians
вот зачитаю э как насколько русских
are being squeezed out of all the national republics,
выдавливают из национальных республик
so now now now now I
всех так вот сейчас сейчас сейчас у меня
was directly saved Look, in
прямо было сохранено Вот смотри в
Ingushetia, Russians in general are less than 1% 0.78
Ингушетии русских вообще меньше 1% 0,78
in Chechnya Russians are
в Чечне русских
1.93 about less than 2  % of all Russians from Chechnya
1,93 про меньше 2% всех русских из Чечни
were squeezed out by the Chechens They come to you in
выдавили чеченцы Приезжают к вам в
Moscow in St. Petersburg They consider themselves
Москву в Питер они считают себя
the masters Well, you yourself think in Chechnya
хозя Ну вот вы сами подумайте в Чечне
what Russians should do in Chechnya, it’s clear that
что русским делать в Чечне понятно что
everyone is moving to Moscow now That’s
все в Москву сейчас переезжают Вот
exactly all the Russians that were squeezed out of Chechnya
именно всех русских выдавили из Чечни Да
Yes, Yakutia Tatarstan also Mariev  that
вот Якутия Татарстан также мариев то
is, look everywhere at the number of Russians under the
есть везде смотри количество русских при
Soviet Union, if I'm not mistaken in the
Советском Союзе в если я не ошибаюсь в в
late eighties, yes. In Yakutia,
конце восьмидесятых да В Якутии
the majority were Russians now Russians.
большинство было русских сейчас русских
In Yakutia,
В Якутии осталось
37% remained. The Yakuts are pushing out Russians from Russian
37% якуты вытесняют русских из русских
republics from their national republics;
респу из своих национальных республик
moreover, Russians are already being pushed out from
больше того русских вытесняют уже и из
classical Russians  regions, what
классических русских регионах что
is happening in the Kaluga region, you I think you
делается в Калужской области вы Я думаю
know, this is such a migrant hub, it’s
Знаете это такой мигрантский хаб уже
just true. Well, now, by the way, they are
просто правда Ну да сейчас кстати очень
fighting them very hard, but they are fighting, they are not
сильно с ними борятся так борятся не
fighting. All of you have already fallen into this trap
борятся Всё вы уже попали в эту ловушку
and you will not be able to do anything with you,
и вы уже ничего не сделаете у вас
technologically you are nothing to them  Replace
технологически вы их никем не Замените
in many schools in the Russian Federation there are
во многих школах э Российской Федерации
already more non-Russians than Russians, and
не русских уже больше чем русских а
school is exactly the future, what will happen
школа - это как раз будущее что будет
in 20 years, you go to school and see,
через 20 лет заходишь в школу и смотришь
uh,
да ээ
ethnic
этнические банды
youth gangs are just pinching Russians, so I’m
молодёжные просто щемят русских вот я
subscribed to different ones, I monitor there’s just
подписан на разные я монитор просто в
all sorts of movements in Russia  there are and what kind of
России всякие движухи есть а какие можно
secrets you can say, you can say that they are completely
есть секрет можете сказать абсолютно
different, both left and right, so if
разные и левые и правые вот если по
that’s why you think it’s multinational, this
этому что вам это многонационал вот этот
Telegram channel has
Telegram канальчик там
some of these anti-minds, they’re just
какие-то эти антиминс они просто их
cool to read because they immediately
клёво читаешь потому что они сразу
collect all sorts of ethnic fights,
коллекционируют всякие этнические драки
some crimes and  you don’t have to
какие-то преступления и всё не надо
climb anything, you don’t have to monitor anything, you just
лазить ничего мониторить только их
look at them and you already see the situation in
смотришь и уже Видишь ситуацию вот в
many Russian schools, the Russians
многих российских школах уже русские
are already in a non-
Как так фактически находятся в не
privileged position, so you
привилегированном положении вот так
can
можно
say and can’t do
сказать и ничего не могут сделать
anything, I let it all
ничего всё
go, I told you that I’m the king of the TsPSO I’m the
попустил я вам казал что я король цпсо Я
king of the TsPSO  I
король цпсо
just let the
само
pies get high, I just
пирожков кайф Я просто
get high, I just
Кайфую я кайфую просто
get high, everything from the dudes is all Greatness
кайфую всё у чуваков всё Величие
was broken in the address letter on Telegram right at
ломалось в дрес пись на й Telegram прямо
the same time, but for now it’s even
зараз он а
more and more respectful YouTube taking
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the scum of ODS in your ban and I
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people  Sometimes we don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we can write an operative link
того чтоб мы ма оперативный звязок
directly at the same time while there in Telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrimm vdeo ezh Tsikava and Korisna
окрим вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and I’m sorry for you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
fast operative link
постный оперативный звязок
independantly in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini pis
YouTube Слава украини пись